Guide to the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records, 1910-2009; 5739-001; 26.52 cubic feet 31 boxes
  - Series III: Contract Negotiations, 1950-2009 (Box-folder 16/1-16/47; 17/1-17/61; 18/1-18/40; 19/1-19/43; 21/1-21/94; 22/1-22/68; 23/1-23/78; 24/1-24/74; 25/1-25/86; 26/1-26/97; 27/1-27/73; 28/1-28/101; 29/1-29/94; 30/1-30/64)
    - Subseries A: Contract Negotiations Part I, 1950-1991 (Box-folder 16/1-16/47; 17/1-17/61; 18/1-18/40; 19/1-19/43)
      - Mars Electric Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1973-1982 (Box-folder 16/41)
      - Marine Controls, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 16/42)
      - Marine Power and Equipment Company Contract Negotiations, 1968 (Box-folder 16/43)
      - Martin Fuel Company Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 16/44)
      - M. B. Electrical Contractors, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1979 (Box-folder 16/45)
      - M. C. Energy Systems Contract Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 16/46)
      - MMR Coporation Contract Negotiations, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 16/47)
      - M and S Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1983 (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Mad Dog Electric, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Mad's Electric Contract Negotiation, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 17/3)
      - Mason's Electrical Service, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Maxwell's Electric, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 17/5)
      - McCoy Electric Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 17/6)
      - McIntyre Electric Contract Negotiations, 1976 (Box-folder 17/7)
      - Van S. McKenny Company Contract Negotiations, 1964-1983 (Box-folder 17/8)
      - McKinstry Company Contract Negotiations, 1965-1986 (Box-folder 17/9)
      - McLennan's Electric Contract Negotiations, 1963-1983 (Box-folder 17/10)
      - McMullen Electric Contract Negotiations, 1974-1984 (Box-folder 17/11)
      - McPheeters Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 17/12)
      - McWik Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1967-1989 (Box-folder 17/13)
      - Melang Brothers Radio & T.V. Contract Negotiations, 1950-1974 (Box-folder 17/14)
      - Meller Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/15)
      - Meridian Center Electric Contract Negotiations, 1971-1982 (Box-folder 17/16)
      - Meyer Sign Company Contract Negotiations, 1971-1990 (Box-folder 17/17)
      - Midway Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 17/18)
      - Mike's Radio & T.V. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 17/19)
      - Miller Oil Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box-folder 17/20)
      - Modular Electric Contract Negotiations, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 17/21)
      - Moose City Service Electric Contract Negotiations, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 17/22)
      - Moses Electric Contract Negotiations, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 17/23)
      - Mosler Airmatic & Electronics System Division Contract Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/24)
      - Multi-Strut Contract Negotiations, 1985 (Box-folder 17/25)
      - Donald B. Murphy Contractors, Incorporated & Associates Contract Negotiations, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 17/26)
      - NABCO Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 17/27)
      - National Sign Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 17/28)
      - Neal Electric Contract Negotiations, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17/29)
      - NEMCO Electric Contract Negotiations, Part 1/3, 1957-1986 (Box-folder 17/30)
      - NEMCO Electric Contract Negotiations, Part 2/3, 1957-1986 (Box-folder 17/31)
      - NEMCO Electric Contract Negotiations, Part 3/3, 1957-1986 (Box-folder 17/32)
      - Neon Acme Sign Company Contract Negotiations, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 17/33)
      - Neonex Sign Corporation Contract Negotiations, 1977 (Box-folder 17/34)
      - NECA (National Electrical Contractors Association) Contract Negotiations, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 17/35)
      - NECA (National Electrical Contractors Association)/IBEW Navy Project, 1986 (Box-folder 17/36)
      - Nesheim Electric Contract Negotiations, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 17/37)
      - Nims Electric, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1965-1988 (Box-folder 17/38)
      - Nolet Electric Contract Negotiations, 1970-1989 (Box-folder 17/39)
      - Norby Electric Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 17/40)
      - North City Electric Contract Negotiations, 1961-1975 (Box-folder 17/41)
      - Northgate Electric Contract Negotiations, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 17/42)
      - Northern Electric Contract Negotiations, 1977-1978; 1989 (Box-folder 17/43)
      - North Pacific Electrical Constructors, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 17/44)
      - Northwest Cablevision (Division of Teleprompter) Contract Negotiations, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 17/45)
      - Northwest Communication Contractors Association Contract Negotiations, Part 1/3, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 17/46)
      - Northwest Communication Contractors Association Contract Negotiations, Part 2/3, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 17/47)
      - Northwest Communication Contractors Association Contract Negotiations, Part 3/3, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 17/48)
      - Northwestern Crane, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17/49)
      - Northwest Electric Sales Company Contract Negotiations, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 17/50)
      - Northwest Industries, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1973-1990 (Box-folder 17/51)
      - Northwest Neon & Plastics, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 17/52)
      - Northwest Ordinance Contract Negotiations, 1968 (Box-folder 17/53)
      - Nottingham Electric Contract Negotiations, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 17/54)
      - S-M Electronics Company Contract Negotiations, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 17/55)
      - Safe-T-Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1955-1969 (Box-folder 17/56)
      - Scalzo International, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 17/57)
      - W.C. Schafer Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 17/58)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company - Appliance, Radio and TV Service Center (Seattle) Contract Negotiations, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 17/59)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company - Appliance, Radio and TV Service Center (Bremerton) Contract Negotiations, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 17/60)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company - Pool Stock Division Contract Negotiations, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 17/61)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company - Mail Order Division Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1965-1986 (Box-folder 18/1)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company - Mail Order Division Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1965-1986 (Box-folder 18/2)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company - Coldspot Division Contract Negotiations, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 18/3)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company - Seattle Electric Motor Shop Contract Negotiations, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 18/4)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company Grievances, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 18/5)
      - Seattle Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1975-1990 (Box-folder 18/6)
      - Seattle Electric Works Contract Negotiations, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 18/7)
      - RCA Service Company Contract Negotiations, Part 1/3, 1957-1977 (Box-folder 18/8)
      - RCA Service Company Contract Negotiations, Part 2/3, 1957-1977 (Box-folder 18/9)
      - RCA Service Company Contract Negotiations, Part 3/3, 1957-1977 (Box-folder 18/10)
      - RCA Business Telephone Systems Contract Negotiations, 1989 (Box-folder 18/11)
      - General Electric Consumer Service F/K/A RCA Service Company Contract Negotiations, 1989 (Box-folder 18/12)
      - General Electric Consumer Service F/K/A RCA Service Company Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 18/13)
      - General Electric Consumer Service F/K/A RCA Service Company Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 18/14)
      - Rhodes Electric Contract Negotiations, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Richard G. Wagner, Incorporated D/B/A Wagner Electric Contract Negotiations, 1961-1975 (Box-folder 18/16)
      - Ridgway Packaging Corporation F/K/A Ridgway Lithograph Company Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 18/17)
      - Ridgway Packaging Corporation F/K/A Ridgway Lithograph Company Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 18/18)
      - Rikal Incorporated National Contract Negotiations, 1979 (Box-folder 18/19)
      - R. L. Payne Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1979 (Box-folder 18/20)
      - Rogers Electric Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 18/21)
      - Rohwein Electric, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1873-1983 (Box-folder 18/22)
      - Rosendin Electric, Incorporated, 1975-1984 (Box-folder 18/23)
      - Ross Electric, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18/24)
      - Rossman Electric, Incorporated, 1962-1985 (Box-folder 18/25)
      - Rossoe Furnace Sales Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1980 (Box-folder 18/26)
      - Rossoe, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 18/27)
      - Rowan Northwestern Decorators, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1964-1981 (Box-folder 18/28)
      - Rufener Electric, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 18/29)
      - Ruff Bros. Engineering Contract Negotiations, 1976 (Box-folder 18/30)
      - SBC Sign Services Contract Negotiations, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 18/31)
      - S & S Electric Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 18/32)
      - S & S Sign Company Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1971-1986 (Box-folder 18/33)
      - S & S Sign Company Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1971-1986 (Box-folder 18/34)
      - City of Seattle Contract Negotiations, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 18/35)
      - Housing Authority of the City of Seattle Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1966-1988 (Box-folder 18/36)
      - Housing Authority of the City of Seattle Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1966-1988 (Box-folder 18/37)
      - Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association (Seattle Times and Seattle Post-Intelligencer) Contract Negotiations, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 18/38)
      - Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association (Seattle Times and Seattle Post-Intelligencer) Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 18/39)
      - Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association (Seattle Times and Seattle Post-Intelligencer) Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 18/40)
      - Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association (Seattle Times and Seattle Post-Intelligencer) Contract Negotiations, Part 1/3, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 19/1)
      - Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association (Seattle Times and Seattle Post-Intelligencer) Contract Negotiations, Part 2/3, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 19/2)
      - Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association (Seattle Times and Seattle Post-Intelligencer) Contract Negotiations, Part 3/3, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 19/3)
      - Seattle Service Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 19/4)
      - Seattle School District No.1 Contract Negotiations, 1965-1989 (Box-folder 19/5)
      - Seattle Fuel (Texaco) Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box-folder 19/6)
      - Seattle University Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1971-1990 (Box-folder 19/7)
      - Seattle University Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1971-1990 (Box-folder 19/8)
      - Seelig Fuel Contract Negotiations, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 19/9)
      - Signal Electric, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1968-1982 (Box-folder 19/10)
      - Signco, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 19/11)
      - Skeleton's Radio & TV Contract Negotiations, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 19/12)
      - Skoglund Company of Washington, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 19/13)
      - Smead Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19/14)
      - Smith Brothers Heating Company Contract Negotiations, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 19/15)
      - Bill Smith Company Contract Negotiations, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 19/16)
      - Smithco Heating, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1961-1977 (Box-folder 19/17)
      - Southern California Electrical Construction Company, 1971 (Box-folder 19/18)
      - Sound Oil Company Contract Negotiations, 1957; 1974-1975; 1989 (Box-folder 19/19)
      - South End Electric Contract Negotiations, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19/20)
      - Southgate Electric Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1963-1983 (Box-folder 19/21)
      - Seattle Community College Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 19/22)
      - Seattle Community College Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 19/23)
      - Sentinel Electric Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 19/24)
      - Sentinel Oil Company Contract Negotiations, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 19/25)
      - Sheats Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 19/26)
      - Shoreline School District Contract Negotiations, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 19/27)
      - L. E. Spitzer Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 19/28)
      - Sprig Electric Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 19/29)
      - Standard Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1975 (Box-folder 19/30)
      - Star Machinery Company Contract Negotiations, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 19/31)
      - Starwest Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 19/32)
      - States Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1976 (Box-folder 19/33)
      - Stearns-Roger Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 19/34)
      - Steeck Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 19/35)
      - Sterling Recreation Organization Company F/K/A Sterling Theatres Company Contract Negotiations, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 19/36)
      - Stevenson Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 19/37)
      - Stromberg-Carlson F/K/A Arcata Communications Contract Negotiations, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 19/38)
      - Strouss Electric Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 19/39)
      - Sun Industries & Associates Contract Negotiations, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 19/40)
      - Superior Electric Service Contract Negotiations, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 19/41)
      - Sunshine Electric Contract Negotiations, 1976 (Box-folder 19/42)
      - Swift Electric Contract Negotiations, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 19/43)
    - Subseries B: Contract Negotiations Part 2, 1952-2009 (Box-folder 21/1-21/94; 22/1-22/68; 23/1-23/78; 24/1-24/74; 25/1-25/86; 26/1-26/97; 27/1-27/73; 28/1-28/101; 29/1-29/94; 30/1-30/64)
      - ABAMP Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991 (Box-folder 21/1)
      - ABC Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 21/2)
      - AC Electric Service (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1993 (Box-folder 21/3)
      - Ace Electric Inc. (Voice-Data-Video) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 21/4)
      - Ace Electric Service (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 21/5)
      - ACS Dataline of the Northwest, Inc. F/K/A Fiber Optics of the Northwest (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1996-2006 (Box-folder 21/6)
      - Action Plus Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 21/7)
      - Adaptive Controls, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 21/8)
      - Advanced Electrical Services (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box-folder 21/9)
      - Advanced Communications Networks, Inc. (Sound & Communication), 2003-2004 (Box-folder 21/10)
      - Advanced Electric & Alarm Systems (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 21/11)
      - Advanced Electric & Alarm Systems (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 21/12)
      - Advanced Electric & Alarm Systems (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 21/13)
      - Advance Systems Integrated (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 21/14)
      - Affordable Crane (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 21/15)
      - Alco Electric LLC (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2006 (Box-folder 21/16)
      - Alco Electric LLC (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2007 (Box-folder 21/17)
      - Aleut Northwest Services (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2005 (Box-folder 21/18)
      - Alindeska Electrical Contractors (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2008 (Box-folder 21/19)
      - Alindeska Electrical Contractors (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004 (Box-folder 21/20)
      - All Construction Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 21/21)
      - Alliance Integrated Systems (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 21/22)
      - All Phase Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21/23)
      - All Points Electric (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 21/24)
      - All Points Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 21/25)
      - Allstate Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 21/26)
      - Alpine Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 21/27)
      - Alpine Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 21/28)
      - Al's Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991, 2004 (Box-folder 21/29)
      - Amco Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2007 (Box-folder 21/30)
      - American District Telegraph Company Contract Negotiations, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 21/31)
      - Americo Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 21/32)
      - Amisson Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 21/33)
      - Anderson Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 21/34)
      - Anderson Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-2009 (Box-folder 21/35)
      - Apex Electric Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 21/36)
      - Apple Electric Contract Negotiations, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 21/37)
      - Appliance Service Station Contract Negotiations, 1991-2005 (Box-folder 21/38)
      - Aquarius Pump Co. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 21/39)
      - Artisan Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 21/40)
      - Art Pearson Electric Contract Negotiations, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 21/41)
      - Associated Builders and Contractors Membership Information, 1982 (Box-folder 21/42)
      - Associated Electric & Alarm, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 21/43)
      - Associated Electric & Alarm, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 21/44)
      - Associated Electric & Alarm, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21/45)
      - Atkinson Bell Electric Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box-folder 21/46)
      - At Your Service Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 21/47)
      - At Your Service Electric, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2006 (Box-folder 21/48)
      - Auburn Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-2003 (Box-folder 21/49)
      - Auburn Electric Co. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21/50)
      - Auburn Electric Co. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 21/51)
      - A.V.E.C., Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 21/52)
      - A.V.E.C., Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 21/53)
      - A. Wilcox Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1961-2003 (Box-folder 21/54)
      - Azar Technical & Electric Contract Negotiations, 1991, 2009 (Box-folder 21/55)
      - B & S Communications, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1984-1994 (Box-folder 21/56)
      - Baird-Weber Enterprises, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-2006 (Box-folder 21/57)
      - Baird-Weber Enterprises, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2006 (Box-folder 21/58)
      - Ball-Foster Glass Packaging Corporation (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 21/59)
      - Barker Electric Co., Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 21/60)
      - Barkhurst Control Technologies, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 21/61)
      - Barkhurst Control Technologies, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 21/62)
      - Barkhurst Control Technologies, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2006 (Box-folder 21/63)
      - Baugh Industrial Contractors, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 21/64)
      - Bayles Brothers, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 21/65)
      - Bayley Electric Service Co. Contract Negotiations, 1969-1989 (Box-folder 21/66)
      - BBC Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 21/67)
      - Beacon Electric Contract Negotiations, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 21/68)
      - Beary Electric Contract Negotiations, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 21/69)
      - Bech Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1965-1977, 1990 (Box-folder 21/70)
      - Beckstrom's Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 21/71)
      - Bee Dandy Inc. D/B/A Bee Dandy Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 21/72)
      - Bee Dandy Inc. D/B/A Bee Dandy Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2007 (Box-folder 21/73)
      - Bee Dandy Inc. D/B/A Bee Dandy Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2007 (Box-folder 21/74)
      - Bellevue Electric Service (Inside Wire/Residential/Stockman/Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1987 (Box-folder 21/75)
      - Bellevue Electric Service (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1986-1995, 2009 (Box-folder 21/76)
      - Bellevue Electric Service & MacDonald-Miller Co. Contract Negotiations, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 21/77)
      - Bellevue Heating & Air Condition Co. Contract Negotiations, 1975 (Box-folder 21/78)
      - Bemis Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 21/79)
      - Benaroya Co. Contract Negotiations, 1971 (Box-folder 21/80)
      - Bird Electric Corp. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1973-1975, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 21/81)
      - Blackbox Network Services (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 21/82)
      - Black's Electrical, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 21/83)
      - Black Tie Communications, Productions Enterprise Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 21/84)
      - Blessing Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 21/85)
      - Block Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2004 (Box-folder 21/86)
      - Block Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 21/87)
      - Blodgett Construction Association, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 21/88)
      - Blue Ribbon Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 21/89)
      - Blyco Electronics Contract Negotiations, 1976 (Box-folder 21/90)
      - BMWC Constructors, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 21/91)
      - Bogden Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 21/92)
      - Bon Marche Contract Negotiations, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 21/93)
      - Border Contractor, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 21/94)
      - Bowie Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1960-1977 (Box-folder 22/1)
      - Bowie Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1987-2000 (Box-folder 22/2)
      - Bowie Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 22/3)